Guide to the Edward J. McCluskey Papers SC1112
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Edward J. McCluskey papers
undated
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
McCluskey, Edward J.
SC1112
99 Linear Feet
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
Professor McCluskey worked on electronic switching systems at the Bell Telephone Laboratories from 1955 to 1959. In 1959, he moved to Princeton University, where he was Professor of Electrical Engineering and Director of the University Computer Center. In 1966, he joined Stanford University, where he is Professor of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, as well as Director of the Center for Reliable Computing. He founded the Stanford Digital Systems Laboratory (now the Computer Systems Laboratory) in 1969 and the Stanford Computer Engineering Program (now the Computer Science MS Degree Program) in 1970. The Stanford Computer Forum (an Industrial Affiliates Program) was started by Dr. McCluskey and two colleagues in 1970 and he was its Director until 1978.
Professor McCluskey developed the first algorithm for designing combinational circuits - the Quine-McCluskey logic minimization procedure as a doctoral student at MIT. At Bell Labs and Princeton, he developed the modern theory of transients (hazards) in logic networks and formulated the concept of operating modes of sequential circuits. His Stanford research focuses on logic testing, synthesis, design for testability, and fault-tolerant computing. Prof. McCluskey and his students at the Center for Reliable Computing worked out many key ideas for fault equivalence, probablilistic modelling of logic networks, pseudo-exhaustive testing, and watchdog processors. He collaborated with Signetics researchers in developing one of the first practical multivalued logic implementations and then worked out a design technique for such circuitry.
Dr. McCluskey served as the first President of the IEEE Computer Society. He is the recipient of the 1996 IEEE Emanuel R. Piore Award. He is a Fellow of the IEEE, AAAS, and ACM; and a member of the NAE. He has honorary doctorates from the University of Grenoble and Bowdoin College. He has published several books including two widely used texts.
[source: http://www-crc.stanford.edu/users/ejm/McCluskey_Edward.html]
McCluskey, Edward J.
- Administrative files
  - Administrative Associate II Search, 1947, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abdel-Hafez, Khader, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abet, 2000 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abraham, Jacob, 1988, 1992, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACM Membership, 1988, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Admitted Applicants Day, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advantest File, 2003 July 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advantest, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advisee, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Tadashi AE, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - V.K. Agarwal, 1987, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aitken, Rob Dr., 1995 March 13 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Altera, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Altsys, 1994 Nov. 15 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alternative System Concepts, Inc., 1994 Nov. 3 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AMBIT, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Amer, Hassanein, 1983-1987, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Express, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - American Institute of Engineers, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - An, Fu-Tai, 1996, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Anderson, Robert, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Andrews, Dorothy, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Apaydin, Mehmet, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Archambeau, Eric, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Argos, 1997 Jan 21-22 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Argos, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - AT&T, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Avizienis, Algirdas, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - AVRA, LaNae, 1988-1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Balteanu, Florinel, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Banerjee, Prith, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bardell, Paul, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Befa, Vlad, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Boley, Dan, 1989, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bose, Bella, 1986-1988, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Boute, Raymond, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Letter from WM. Bowen, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bozorgui-Nesbat, Saied, 1983-1985, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bracewell, Ron, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Brokaw, Dave, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Brothers, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Brown, Becky, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Butner, Steve, 1981, 1984, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Butts, Mike, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cadat, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cadence, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Campos, Lorraine, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cats, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Cazares, Norma, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Chang, Ben, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Chang, Jonathan Tsung-Yung, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Chen, Qingfang, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Chen, Ray, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Cheng, Kan-Yuan, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Cheng, Kwang-Ting (Tim), 1995 21 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Cheng, Yu-Che Eddie, 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Chin, Cary, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Cho, Sang-Bock, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Chu, Yi-Chin, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - CAD Day Programs, 2000 Nov. 9 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - CAD Day '00, 2000 Nov. 9 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - CAD Day '99, 1999 Nov. 11 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - CAD Day, 1998 Nov. 12 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - CAD Day, 1997 Nov. 13 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - CAD Day, 1996 Nov. 14 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - CAD Day, 1995 Nov. 9 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - CAD Day, 1994 Nov. 10 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - CAD Day, 1993 Nov. 11 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - CAD Day, 1992 Nov. 13 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - CAD Day, 1991 Nov. 14 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - CAD Day, 1990 Nov. 15 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - CAD Day, 1989 Nov. 9 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Chip Engines, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - CIS, 1982, 1989-1991, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - CIS, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Recommendation for Se June Hong, 2002 Dec. 6 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - CLSI, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Chillarege, Ram, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Computer Forum Visits, 1981, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Department of Computer Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Consulting, 1977-1978, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Courses and Degrees, 1986, 1991, 1993, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Crosscheck, 1993 Sept. 13 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - CSD Advisory Committee, 1977, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - CSD, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - CSL File, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Cortes, Mario L., 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Copyright Information, 1985, 1992-1995, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Current, Wayne, 1980-1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cutler, James, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - D and T, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - d'Abreu, Manuel, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - DARPA: Dept Army Acquisition, 2001 Oct. 26 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Visiting Prof: Accepted Dandapani, Ramaswami, Prof., 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - DAS, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - David, Rene, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Demirkol, Mehmet Kursad, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Info, 1978, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - D'Souza, Daniel, 1993 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Duell, Bob, 1998 June 29 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Deans Report, 2003-2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Deans Report, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Deans Report, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Deans Report, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Deans Report, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Deans Report, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Deans Report, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Deans Report, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Deans Report, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Deans Report, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Deans Report, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Deans Report, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Deans Report, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Deans Report, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Deans Report, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Deans Report, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Deans Report, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Deans Report, 1986 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - President's Report, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Thanks from J.F. McDonald (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Administrative: President's Report, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Administrative: President's Report, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Administrative: President's Report, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Administrative: President's Report, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Administrative: President's Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Administrative: President's Report, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - EE Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Eichelberger, Ed, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Electronic Letters Request to Review Paper, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Elsevier North-Holland, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Ersoz, Aydin, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Engineering Advisory Council, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Engineering Library Committee, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Fasang, Pat, 1998 Apr 3 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Fazil, M.M., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Fields, Charles, 1991 Dec 3 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Fleming, Lee, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Franco, Piero, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Freeman, Gregory G., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Fuchs, W. Kent, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Fridman, Vladmir, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Fujitsu Corporation, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Fukada, Kaoru, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Fukao, Kazuichi, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Fukazawa, Tomoo, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Furuya, Riyoshi, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - $ Gifts Received, 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Gartner, Dr. Peter, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - GATES Building, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - GATEWAY, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - GENRAD - General File, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - General Electric, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - GenRad, 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Gerbaux, Laurent, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Gheewala, Tushar, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Giomi, Jean Charles, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Gobbi, Jose-M., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Gogolewski, Mark Raymond, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Golomb, Solomon, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Goosen, Hendrik, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Guermeur, Daniel, 1989 Feb-1988 Sep (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Gupta, Sandeep K., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Ha, Dong, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Hassan, Syed Zahoor, 1983-1999 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Hayes, Dr. John P., 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Hennessy, John L., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Hao, Hong, 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Hao 92-Analysis of Gate Oxide Shorts in CMOS Circuits, 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Hawkins, Charles F., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Hong, Darlene, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Hua, Duc, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Huang, Wei-Je Robert, 1996-2001 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Hughes Aircraft Company, 1978-1996 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Hughes, Joseph, 1983-1992 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Huston, Robert, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - IBM, 1992, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - IBM, 1977, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - IEEE Distinguished Visitors, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - IEEE, 1980-1983, 1993, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - IEEECS Design & Test Journal, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - IEEE Computer Society, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Form "IEEE Fellow Nomination" from Dr. Ray Mercer, Texas AVM, 2002 March (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - IEEE Computer Society Press, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - IEEE - Student Branch, 1995-2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - IEEE Emanuel R. Piore Award, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Saxena 92-Simple Bounds on Signature Analysis Aliasing for Random Testing Saxena, Franco, EJM IEEE Trans. Comput, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - IEEE Press, 1995 July (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Ishizuka, Oshiko, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Ivanov, Andre, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Intel, 2003 Feb. 11 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Iyer, Ravi, 1979-2000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Jha, Niraj, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - JPL (Jet Propulsion Laboratory), 1962 Nov. 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Kamath, Rejesh, 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Kan, Erin, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Kandukuri, Sunil, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Karrfalt, Jake, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Khunpitiluck, Chat, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Kim, Moon-Jung, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Kimura, Tsunekazu, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - KOE, Wern-Yan, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Koguchi, Yukio, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Sol Shatz, 1997 April 22 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Kosalge, Sunil, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Krishnamurthy, Balaji, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Kunii, Tosiyasu, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Innovative Claims for the Proposed Research, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Draper Labs, 1998 Nov. 13 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Wasim Azhar, 1998 Oct. 20 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Adil Ahmed Sherwani, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Lau, Cliff, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Lee, Cathy, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Lerner, Mark, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Lo, Vincent, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - LogicVision, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Lu, Davia, 1983-1988, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Makar, Samy, 1988-1997 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Malek, Miroslaw, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Mange, Daniel, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Marda, Vikash, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Marhoeffer, Michael, 1986-1989, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Masuyama,Hiroshi, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Martino, Sergio, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Martionolle, Francoise, 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Maxwell, Peter, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Maxumder, Pinaki, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - MCC, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - McCluskey, David, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - McClusky, Edward J. Awards, 1991-2001 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - McClusky, Edward (Sabbatical), 1987-2002 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - EJM 70th, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - McClusky, E.J. (Personal Information), 1983-2001 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - McCluskey, Joseph, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Mcgraw-Hill Book Company, 1980-1983, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Meng, Teresa, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Mentor Graphics, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Mercer, M. Ray, 1985-1996 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Millman, Steven D., 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Min, Yinghua, 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Mitsubishi, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Montemayor, Carlos, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Morgan Kaufman Contract, 2002 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Motohara, Akira, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mourad, Samiha, 1982-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mukund, Shridhar, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Muroga, Saburo, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Muroi, Katsunobu, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Takshi Nanya, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - N.K. Nanda RE: Visit CRC (Visiting Scholar), 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NASA, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Needham, Wayne, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Niamat, Mohammed, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National Semiconductor, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - No-Cost Extension Requests, 1993, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Norman, Bob, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Norwood, Rob, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Nondisclosure Agreements, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Nowick, Steven, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NSF Proposal Reviews, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NUR = Proposal, 1996 Sept. 2 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NDA Stanford, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Offic of Technology Licensing, 2003 July 23 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Oh, Nahm Suk, 1995-2001 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - OPMAXX, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Ohno, Yutaka, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Osbrow, Richard, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Permissions, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Prentice Hall, Inc., 1987-2003 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Pan, Rong, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Students, Potential F Parkin, Michael William, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Marian Party KA -Comments on Papers, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Janak Patel, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Robert Pease IEEE Fellow Grade Reference Form, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Permission and Copyright NSF, 2002 Feb. 2 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Pho Quals, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Pierce, John, 1993 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Plusquellic, James, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Pomeranz, Irith, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Pradhan, Dhirai, 1993-2000 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Philips NDA, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Philips, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Piore Awards, 2004 Jan. 29 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Piore Awards (Brever, M.), 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Pradhan, Dhiraj K. (Visitor), 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Prokin, Milan, 1992 March 23 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Public Access Files, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - PYCON, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Ph. D Quals, 1975-1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Qualifying Exams, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Quals, 1990 Jan. 22-25 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Quals Appeals, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Quals, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Quals, 1994 Jan. 24-28 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Quals, 1993 Jan. 25-29 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Quals, 1995 Jan. 23-27 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Quals, 1996 Jan. 22-26 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Quals, 1997 Jan. 27-31 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - IDEA668, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Quals, 1998 Jan. 12-16 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Quals, 1999 Jan. 11-15 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Quals, 2000 Jan. 10-14 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - PHD Qualifying Exam, 2000 Jan. 10-14 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Quals Appeals, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Quals, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Quals, 2001 Jan. 22-26 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Quals, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Raytheon, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Tony Ralston Re: Logic Design, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - C.V. Ramamoorthy, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - RATS/EE385A, 1996-1997 Spring (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Reddy, Sudhakar M., 1986-1991 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Redinbo, Robert G., 1990, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Reference Data for Radio Engineers, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Reference Data for Radio Engineers, 1985, 1992, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Retirement, 1994 May 12 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Retreat, 1992 Sept.-Nov. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Riedel, Marc, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Alan Ross Resume, 1999 Feb. 8 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Alan Ross Proposal, 1997 June 5 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Board Design and Email, 1997 May (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Saab, Daniel, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Saito, Nobuo, 1996 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Students: Sakov, Josh, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Salisbury, Allan, 1996 May (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sanechika, Noriaki, 1967, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Sartori, Gian Luigi, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Saucier, Gabrielle IEEE Fellowship, 1990 April 30 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Savier, Jacob, 1975-1979, 1989,1992-1996 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Scanner, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Schlumberger, 1992, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Schneeweiss, Winfrid, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - School of Engineering, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Sedmak, Richard, 1987, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Sematech, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Shamseldin, Adel, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Seok-Bung, Han, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Shedletsky, John J., 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - John Shen, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Shen, Paul, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Shirvani, Philip P., 1996, 1998, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Shperling, Itzhak, 1988, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Siegman, Tony, 1973 Aug. 13 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Siewiorek, Daniel P., 1969-1972, 1975, 1978, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Sipple, Regina Spencer, 1994 March 3 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - SITN, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Sony, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Stanford Cmoputer Forum, 2002 Feb. 25 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Stroud, Charles, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Subscriptions, 1989, 1993, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Equipment Inventory-SUN, 1998 June (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Sun Software Maintenencce, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Sun (server) Purchase, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Sun Workstation, 1993, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Sun, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Sunrise, 1995 May (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Switching Theory Article, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Synplicity, 1999 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Svobodova, Liba, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Syntest, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Sziray, Jozsef, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Paul Bohn, U. of Illinois, 2001 Dec. 4 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Tadashi, Ae., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Tan, Rudy, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Tanno, Kuninobu, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Tatsuta, Toyokazu, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Office of Technology Licensing, 2001, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Teradyne, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Test technology Technical Committee, 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Tohma. Yshihiro, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Thomson - CSF Ventures, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Texas Instruments Electronics, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Tobagi, F.A., 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Tokarnia, Alice, 1992, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Synthesis of Random Pattern testable Circuits with Test, 1996, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Touba, Nur, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Professor Trivedi, 1986, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Udell, Jon G., Jr., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Counters (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - SEQ/ Hennie, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - IBM Field Engin. 360/30 2030 Process Unit, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Introduction to the Theory of Switching Cicuits, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Micro, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Princeton University Group Codes, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Maunfaturing Test Research Symposium, 1999 Oct. 13 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - NAE Congratulations, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - WASH, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - AFIPS Inforamtion Center in Washington D.C., 1974 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - EJM MMS, 1956-1958 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - ECO System Lectures 36-45, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - MIT Computation Book Course 6332 McCluskey Notes, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Boolean Algebra, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Error Correction Code Paper, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Algebraic Minimization and the Design of Two-Terminal Contact Networks, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Center for Reliable Computing CRC Publications, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Int'l Sumposiums on fault-Tolerant Computing, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Center for Reliable Computing Summary, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - McCluskey - Gschwind Chapters 8-10, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - McCluskey-Gschwind Chapters 1-7, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Logic Design Prof. E.J. McCluskey, 1984 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - EE381/CS211 Logic Design Duplicate, 1980-1981 Winter (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - MIT Statistical Theory of Cimmunication and Notes, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Computer Reliability Bibliography, 1970 Oct. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Functional Testing A State of the Art Survey, 1985 Nov. 18 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Suisse, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 311 Misc, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Leiner, 1959, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - G.A. Maley J. Earle, 1960 July 20 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - G.A. Maley & J. Earle, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lloyd, 1957 March (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Linvill, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - ICCAD, 1989 Oct. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - RATS, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lutz, Bruce C., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Manner, Reinhard, 1981 Oct. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Manninen, Markku, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Mantley, Dr. Patrick, 1978 May (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Masreliez, C. Johan, 1975 Oct. (Box 19, Folder 16)